Leviathan is a documentary film directed by Lucien Castaing-Taylor.
An experimental portrait of the North American commercial fishing industry through the lens
of GoPro cameras placed on a fishing vessel off the coast of New England.
Himself, played by Declan Conneely.
Himself, played by Johnny Gatcombe.
Himself, played by Adrian Guillette.
Himself, played by Brian Jannelle.
Himself, played by Clyde Lee.
Himself, played by Arthur Smith.
Leviathan is a 2012 American documentary directed by Lucien Castaing-Taylor and
Véréna Paravel of the Sensory Ethnography Lab at Harvard University.
It is a work about the North American fishing industry.
The film was acquired for U.S.
distribution by The Cinema Guild.
The film-makers used GoPro cameras and worked twenty-hour
shifts during the shooting of the film.
The film explores themes of fishing, atlantic ocean, fisherman, woman director.